A Finding Aid to the Samuel J. Wagstaff Papers, circa 1932-1985, in the Archives of American Art AAA.wagssamu
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1932-1986; Series 1; (Boxes 1-3, 8, OV 9-10; 2.5 linear ft.)
  - Correspondence concerning Photography, 1957-1985; 1.2
    - Halus, Siegfried - Iverson, Brad, 1971-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
      Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc.
      Harry N. Abrams, Inc.
      Harwey, Thom
      Hass, Kevin
      Haworth-Booth, Mark
      Hayes, Maryanne
      Helter, Sylviane
      Henle, Jan
      Hetzler, Max
      Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden
      Hochmann, John L.
      Hollander, Michael S.
      Hopps, Walter
      Hoshour Gallery
      Hovland, Charles
      Howard Ricketts, Limited
      Howard S. Mott, Inc.
      Hulick, Diane
      Hulsey, Charles
      Hyde, Scott
      Hyman, Roger
      IBM Gallery of Science and Art
      Idea Books
      International Center for Photography
      Iverson, Brad
    - Jacobs, David A. - Kurzner, Lisa, 1975-1984, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
      Jacobs, David A.
      Jaeger, Stefan de
      Jammes, André
      Jargon Society, Inc.
      Jeffers, Jack
      Jeffersen, J. W.
      Joan Perkal Books
      John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation
      John Michael Kohler Arts Center
      John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
      John Weber Gallery
      Jones, Edward Powis
      Jones, Peter C.
      Jones, Renee
      Judson, Bill and Leo Castellli
      Juracek, Jan
      Jurka, Rob
      Kaplan, Albert
      Kaplan, Daile
      Karnick, Irwin
      Kathleen Ewing Gallery (see also: Quindacqua, Ltd.)
      Katz, Leandro
      Keyes, Donald D.
      Kilian, Karl
      Kimmel/Cohn Photography Arts
      Kingston, Rodger R.
      Koch, Lewis
      Kolbert, Frank
      Konetzni, Al
      Koopman, Rick
      Kopp, Joel
      Korn, Pearl
      Kouwenhoven, John
      Kraft, Steven
      Kunsthaus Zürich
      Kurzner, Lisa
    - L., Tom - Lyon, Mark, 1975-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
      L. Tom
      Laffaire, Jean-Jacques
      Last, Yong-Hee
      Laufer, Susan B.
      Laurence G. Miller, Inc.
      Laviosa, Angelo
      Leatherdale, Marcus
      Lebe, David
      Ledel Gallery
      Lehr, Janet
      Lerner, Norman
      Levin, Janice
      Levin, Robert J.
      Levine, Henriette and Neal
      Levy, Gérard
      Levy, Vibeke
      Libourel, André-Jean
      Life
      Light
      Lindemann, Edward
      Lindroth, Linda
      Linn, Judy
      Lockwood, Maurice de F.
      Lorenz, Richard
      Los Angeles Center for Photographic Studies
      Loykovna, Barbara
      Lucien Goldschmidt, Inc.
      Lunn, Mr. and Mrs. Harry Hyatt, Jr.
      Lynne, Jill
      Lyon, Mark
    - MacMillan Publishing Co., Inc. - Myers, Steve, 1975-1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
      MacMillan Publishing Co., Inc.
      Magalhaes, Bernardo T. S.
      Mahon, Robert
      Male, Lee
      Maloney, Peyton P.
      Mander, Simon
      Mapplethorpe, Robert
      Marcuse Pfeifer Gallery
      Marlborough Gallery, Inc.
      Marmaras, John
      Marsh, Caryl
      Marshall, Nancy
      Mayer, Grace
      Mc ? [illegible], M.
      McCabe, John
      McHugh, R. J.
      McIntosh, M.
      McKenzie, Michael
      Menses
      Metropolitan Museum of Art
      Metzner, Sheila
      Millea, Tom
      Miller, John R.
      Mock, Richard
      Mondale, Joan Adams
      Moers, Denny
      Mones, Arthur
      Monroe, Henry
      Moore, Bette
      Moore, Linda K.
      Muir, Douglas
      Museo del Barrio
      Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles
      Myers, Steve
    - Nabors, Barbara - Ott, R., 1975-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Nabors, Barbara
      National Artists' Alliance Inc.
      National Association of Photographic Manufacturers, Inc.
      National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
      National Portrait Gallery, London
      Neikrug Press
      Neuberger Museum
      Neusüss, Floris M.
      New School Art Center, Collectors Institute
      New York Historical Society
      New York Institute of Technology
      New York Photo District News
      New York Public Library
      New York University
      New York University, Grey Art Gallery
      New York University, Photo Center Gallery
      Nexus, Inc.
      Nexus Press
      Nicholas F. Rizzo Fine Arts
      Nilsen, Beate
      Norman, Dorothy
      Northlight
      North Pointe Gallery
      Norton, Russell
      Okuhara, Tetsu
      Okuhn, Jenny
      Olympus Centre
      Oregon Center for the Photographic Arts (see: Blue Sky Gallery)
      Orraca, Jose
      Ostapeck, Lady
      Ostier, André
      Otfinowski, Nanata
      Ott, R.
    - Pace/MacGill - Prossman, Nancy, 1975-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Pace/MacGill
      Parr [?], Richard
      Past and Present Gallery
      Peregrine Smith, Inc.
      Peters, Susan Dodge
      Peterson, Anne E.
      Le Petit Journal
      Phoenix Art Museum
      Phoenix Gallery
      Photographers' Gallery
      Photographic Gallery, University of Southampton
      Photography - Art and Investment
      Photography Gallery
      Pollard, Richard O.
      Popular Photography
      Porter, Allan
      Portfolio
      Portico
      Prashanta, Nirgrantha
      Preservation Publishing Company
      Privitera, Pietro
      Professional Photographers of America, Inc.
      Professional Women Photographers, Inc.
      Prossman, Nancy
    - Quimby, William Floyd - Rosenthal, Richard, 1974-1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Quimby, William Floyd
      Quindacqua, Ltd. (see also Kathleen Ewing Gallery)
      Quitslund, Toby
      R., George
      Rafast, Saam
      Rasmus, David
      Reese, Michael, II
      Reeve, Catherine (Kitty)
      Réunion des Musées Nationaux, Palais du Louvre
      Revlon
      Reynolds, Jock
      RFG Publishing Inc.
      Richards, Eugene
      Richardson, Brigid R.
      Rick Webster Photographic Arts and Services
      Rinhart, George R.
      Ritchie, John (see: Font, Paul and John Ritchie)
      Robert Freidus Gallery, Inc.
      Robert Miller Gallery, Inc.
      Robert Schoelkopf Gallery
      Robinson, David
      Rodman, Don
      Rosen, Nancy
      Rosenthal, Richard
    - Ross, Charles - Ruspoli, A., 1971-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Ross, Charles
      Roth, Joan
      Rouse, Dot
      Rudolph, Nancy
      Rufflé, Jean-Jacques
      Rupp, Sheron
      Ruspoli, A.
    - Salford 80 - Sixth London Photograph Fair, 1975-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Salford 80
      Salloum, Jayce
      Sammlung Fotografis Länderbank
      Sandrow, Hope
      San Francisco Museum of Modern Art
      Sasgen, Peter
      S. A. Shapiro Research Corporation
      Scheinman, Alan
      Schlowsky, Francis
      Schoenfeld, Diana
      Schwartz, A.
      Scimé, Giuliana
      Scriptorium
      Seltzer, Kathleen
      Shannon, Tom
      Shapazian, Robert
      Shapiro, Sid
      Shiebe, Mart H.
      Shiraoka, Jun
      Silver Bullett Gallery, Inc.
      Simon Gallery
      Sinsbaugh, Art
      Sixth London Photograph Fair
    - Smith, Keith A. - Svendsen, Karina E., 1975-1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Smith, Keith A.
      Smith, Mia
      Smith, Michael
      Smith, Stephen
      Solomon, Rosalind
      Sotheby's Belgravia
      Sotheby's, New York
      Space
      Staller, Eric
      Starr, Ron
      Stephen White Gallery of Photography, Inc.
      Stephenson, David M.
      Sterling and Francine Clark Art Institute
      Stern
      Stern, John
      Stern, Marilyn, Andrew and Shirley Goodman
      Stevens, Bruno
      Stock Imagery
      Stolwein, Walter
      Stone, Bill
      Stone, Marly
      Stretch, Bonnie Barrett
      Sunday Times, London
      Super, Gary Lu
      Susan Harder Gallery
      Susan Spiritus Gallery, Inc.
      Sussman, Leonard
      Svendsen, Karina E.
    - Texbraun - Uptown Center Hull House Association, 1975-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Texbraun
      Thackrey and Robertson
      Thames and Hudson, Ltd.
      Thorne-Thomsen, Ruth
      Tice, George A.
      Tighe, Michael
      Traub, Willard
      Tucker, Jean S.
      Tvorik, Stephen J.
      University of New Mexico
      University of Northern Iowa
      University of Texas Press
      Uptown Center Hull House Association
    - Vallarno, Gabrielle - von Matthiessen, Maria, 1976-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Vallarno, Gabrielle
      Van der Zee
      Van Piper, Peter
      Varnedoe, Kirk
      Vermont Crossroads Press
      View Press, Inc.
      Viking Press Inc.
      Vikki Ericks Associates
      Village Cry
      Vision Gallery of Photography
      Visual Arts Research and Resource Center Relating to the Caribbean
      Vogt, Christian
      Vogue
      Vonga, Maurice
      von Matthiessen, Maria
    - Wadsworth Atheneum - Worth, Don, 1974-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Wadsworth Atheneum
      Wallace, Brenda
      Wallen, Don
      Walter, Paul F.
      Walter Reuben, Inc.
      Watari, Shizuko
      Wehrer, Anne
      Weideman, Ryan
      Weidge, Paula
      Weiner, Hilary
      Weiner, Jane
      Weinrich, James D.
      Weinstein, Frank
      Weissman, Naomi
      Wendkos, Gina
      Western Canada Pictorial Index
      Weston, Neil
      Whitney Museum of American Art
      Wildbank, Charles
      Wilkinson, Wilk
      Wilks, Harry
      Wilsey Rare Books
      Winkler, Helen
      Winter, Clark
      Witkin, Joel-Peter
      Wood, Brian
      Worth, Don
    - Yale Unversity Art Gallery - Zolla/Lieberman Gallery, 1974-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Yale University Art Gallery
      Yale University Art Gallery, Friends of American Arts at Yale
      Yarlow/Salzman Gallery
      Yoder, Janica
      Young, Jim
      Zabriskie Gallery
      Zeitlin and ver Brugge Booksellers
      Zetterstrom, Tom
      Zimmerman
      Zola/Lieberman Gallery
    - Illegible, 1976-1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified (enclosures separated from letters), 1967-1975, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Unknown, 1964-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Addison
      B.
      Ben
      Bernard ( see also: Gabriel and Bernard)
      Bill
      Bob
      Carloh
      Carlton
      Charlie
      Colin
      David and [illegible]
      Dick
      Elinor
      Elinor and Joey
      Elizabeth
      François and Gérard
      Gabriel and Bernard
      Gary
      George
      Grace
      Harvey
      Holly
      J.
      Justin
      Max
      Peter
      Richard
      Robert
      Rosalinde
      Royal
      Rudolf
      Ruth
      Scott
      Ted
      Warren
    - Unsigned, 1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Writings, 1961-1983; Series 2; (Box 3; 0.2 linear feet)
  Writings by Wagstaff consist of "Looking at Modern Art" prepared for the Trinity College Reading Program, and an untitled piece about mulitiplicity in art. Among the authors represented are Bruce Bennard, Henry Geldzahler, and Bonnie Barrett Stretch.
  Writings are arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Artists' Statements, 1961-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Manuscripts (Box 3)
    - Bennard, Bruce, "The Photographer Rediscovered,", undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Demarco, Richard, "A Month in Orbit,", undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Geldzahler, Henry, "Pop Art,", undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Sommer, Fred, "Pictorial Logic," Talk at Corcoran Symposium, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Stretch, Bonnie Barrett, "Collecting Photographs: Questions of Art and Commerce,", undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Wagstaff, Samuel J., Jr., "Looking at Modern Art," Trinity College Reading Program, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Wagstaff, Samuel J., Jr., Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Unknown, "Continuity and Change at Hartford,", undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Unknown, "Photographic Portraits" (outline and draft of introduction, with illustrations), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Poem - Unknown, "The Will,", undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Project/Exhibition Proposals (Lisette Model: "The Visual Arts at Black Mountain College"), undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Reminiscences/Obituaries (Jaacob Deschin, Lisette Model), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Papers and Artifacts, 1970s-1980s; Series 3; (Boxes 3, 8; 0.2 linear ft.)
  This series consists of a small amount of artwork, artist resumes, and a costume that consists of a stuffed devil's tail and two red silk caps connected by a long sash and stored in a matching bag.
  Additional artwork, résumes, and some small artifacts may be found attached to correspondence in Series 1: Correspondence.
  - Artifact, undated; (Not scanned) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Artwork (Box 3)
    - Drawings by Bruce Kleinsmith, undated; (see: box 8) (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Print by Harold Paris, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Resumes (A-Z), 1970s-1980s; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
  - Art Work - Drawings by Bruce Kleinsmith, undated; (see also: box 3, folder 32) (Box 8 (sol), Folder 2)
- Printed Material, 1914-1988; Series 4; (Boxes 3-8, OV 11; 3.2 linear ft.)
  The majority of the exhibition catalogs, books, and posters found here concern photography and photographic exhibitions, although a few relate to other media and events. Books, reproductions, and sales catalogs have not been digitized.
  Additional printed material, including many exhibition announcements and press releases, can be found with correspondence in Series 1: Correspondence.
  Material is arranged by record type.
  - Announcements of Published Portfolios (A-Z by Photographer), undated; see also (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Annual Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Articles, 1914, 1964-1979; (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 38-43)
  - Articles, 1980-1984, undated; (5 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
  - Auction Catalogs, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Books, Abish, Walter - Basilico, Gabriele, circa 1968-1978; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Abish, Walter. Cecile Abish Firsthand
    Acker, Cathy and Christian Michelides. Marcus Leatherdale
    Arlene Gottfried
    Basilico, Gabrield. Milano Ambiente Urbano
  - Books, Coleman, A. C. - Gillette, Frank, circa 1978-circa 1980; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Coleman, A. C. (intro) The Southern Ethic
    De Lucia, Nicholas. De Lucia of Light
    Gillette, Frank. Arkansas Axis of Observation
  - Books, Hilliard, John - Ponsold, Renate and Robert Motherwell, cira 1973-circa 1981; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Hilliard, John. Elemental Conditioning
    Loew, Edgar V. The Other Slide
    McGuirk, Paul. Our Anniversary Album (see: Box 8)
    Operation Sail
    Paternite, Stephen. Below the Visible Spectrum
    Ponsold, Renate and Robert Motherwell. Apropos Robinson Jeffers (see Box 8)
  - Books, Schmidt, Michael - Wolfson, Gary, 1974-1981; (Not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Schmidt, Michael. Stadtlandschaften 1981
    Sera, Stephen. Photoworks 1976-1981
    Thomas, George C. Margaree: Photographs of Cape Breton (see: Box 8)
    Webb, Boyd. Tableaux
    Wolfson, Gary. Jeunes Photographes Americains
  - Calendars and Schedules, 1980-1983, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1971-1980, undated; see also (Box 4, Folder 12-24)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1981-1985, undated; see also (Box 5, Folder 1-7)
  - Exhibition Prospectuses, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Service Programs, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Items, 1980, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Periodicals, Afterimage - Art Journal, 1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    After Image (see Box 8)
    American Federiation of Arts Newsletter (see Box 8)
    Appearances
    Art Journal
  - Periodicals, Art-Rite, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Periodicals, Balloon Newspaper - Camerawork Newsletter, 1969-1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Balloon Newspaper
    Blue Sky Bulletin
    Butterfield Bulletin
    Camera Show News
    Camerawork Newsletter
  - Periodicals, Carl Siembab Gallery Newsletter - Cronin Gallery Newsletter, 1975-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Catskill Center for Photography, Center Quarterly
    China Club, Situations (see: Box 8)
    Copyright (see: Box 8)
    Créatis (see: Box 8)
    Cronin Gallery Newsletter
  - Periodicals, European Photography - Friends of Photography Newsletter, 1975-1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    European Photography
    Focal Point Gallery, Viewfinder
    Friends of Photography, Newsletter
  - Periodicals, G. Ray Hawkins Gallery, Photo Bulletin, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Periodicals, Galerie Die Brücke, Inter View - Künstmuseum Düsseldorf, Ausstellungsblätter der Moderne Abeilung, 1974-1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Galerie Die Brücke, Inter View (see Box 8)
    Ground Glass
    Harcus Krakow Gallery Newsletter
    History of Photography, An International Quarterly
    (see: Box 8)
    Kathleen Ewing Gallery Newsletter
    Kunstkritiek Op Komrij Museum Journal
    Künstmuseum Düsseldorf, Ausstellungsblätter der Moderne Abeilung
  - Periodicals, Leica Photography - Palm Beach News, 1974-1983, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Leica Photography
    Manhattan Catalogue (see: Box 8)
    Mancini Gallery, Inc., Preview
    New York University, Grey Art Gallery Bulletin
    Nikon Flash (see: Box 8)
    Northwest Sampler (see Box 8)
    Palm Beach News (see Box 8)
  - Periodicals, Pentax Photography - Photographs: A Collector's Newsletter, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Pentax Photography
    Philadelphia Photo Review
    Photo Reporter
    Photographic Collectors' Newsletter
    Photographs: A Collector's Newsletter
  - Periodicals, Popular Photography - Robert Freidus Gallery Newsletter, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Print Letter
    Professional Women Photographers, PWP Times (see: Box 8)
    Rhode Island School of Design, Ishmael Review of Art and Literature
    Robert Freidus Gallery Newsletter
  - Periodicals, San Francisco Camerawork Quarterly - Traveling Exhibition Information Service, Newsletter, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    San Francisco Camerawork Quarterly
    Society for Photographic Education, Spectrum
    Something Else Newsletter
    Stanford Museum
    Traveling Exhibition Information Service, Newsletter
  - Periodicals, University of Arizona Center for Creative Photography - Wochenpresse Color, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    University of Arizona Center for Creative Photography (untitled newsletter)
    University of New Mexico, College of Fine Arts, New Mexico Studies in the Fine Arts
    University of New Mexico, University Art Museum Bulletin
    Views, A New England Journal of Photography (see: Box 8)
    Village Cry (see: Box 8)
    Wochenpresse Color
  - Periodicals, Zabriskie Photography Newsletter - Zein, 1977-1984 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Zabriskie Photography Newsletter
    Zein (see: Box 8)
  - Posters, 1964-1983, undated; (Not scanned) (Box OV 11)
  - Press Releases, 1965-1985, undated; (12 folders) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 1-12)
  - Reproductions (includes postcards), 1988; see also (Box 7 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Sales Catalogs - Books, Documents, Ephemera, Photographs and Photographic Equipment, 1972-1982, undated; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 2-3)
  - Subscription and Membership Forms, 1982, undated (Box 7 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Symposium, Lecture, and Workshop Announcements and Programs, 1974-1984, undated (Box 7 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Announcements of Published Portfolios (Harry Callaham), 1980; (see also Box 3 F36) (Box 8 (sol), Folder 3)
  - Books, (McGuirk, Paul - Thomas, George), circa 1978-1981; (Not scanned) (Box 8 (sol), Folder 4)
    McGuirk, Paul. Our Anniversary Album, A Photographic Record, circa 1978
    Ponsold, Renate and Robert Motherwell. Apropos Robinson Jeffers, 1981
    Thomas, George C. Margaree: Photographs of Cape Breton, 1980
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1980-1982; (see also Box 5 F1-7) (Box 8 (sol), Folder 5)
  - Periodicals, ( Afterimage - Focal Point Gallery, Viewfinder), circa 1978-1981, undated (Box 8 (sol), Folder 6)
    American Federation of Arts, Newsletter
    China Club, Situations
    Copyright
    Créatis
    Focal Point Gallery Viewfinder
  - Periodicals, (Galerie Die Brücke, Inter View - Professional Women Photographers PWP Times), 1978-1984 (Box 8 (sol), Folder 7)
    Galerie Die Brücke, Inter View
    Manhattan Catalogue
    Nikon Flash
    Northwest Sampler
    Palm Beach News
    Professional Women Photographers, PWP Times
  - Periodicals, ( Views, A New England Journal of Photography - Zion), 1976-1983, undated (Box 8 (sol), Folder 8)
    Views, A New England Journal of Photography
    Zien
  - Reproductions, 1983, undated; (see also Box 7 F1; not scanned) (Box 8 (sol), Folder 9)
- Photographs, 1975-1982; Series 5; (Boxes 7-8; 0.1 linear ft.)
  Photographs consist largely of copy prints and a very small number of original prints filed by photographer. Miscellaneous subjects are book covers and pages, exhibition installations, and an exterior view of the International Center of Photogaphy (Willard Straight house). No images of Samuel J. Wagstaff are included. Among the photographs of people are: Bella Abzug, Michael Collins, Angela Davis, Candy Darling, Wendell Ford, Joseph Hirshhorn, Bettie Ringma, and Andy Warhol, as well as unidentified individuals.
  Additional photographs may be found attached to correspondence (Series 1), and among the writings (Series 4) accompanying a manuscript about portrait photographs.
  Some photographs are arranged by photographer and others by subject.
  - Abramson, Michael - Illegible, 1975-1982, undated; (2 folders) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 6-7)
    Abramson, Michael
    Akiba, David (see: Box 8)
    Atget, Eugene
    Bechard, E.
    Bowers, Harry
    Brown, Lawrie
    Cohen, Mark
    Dawson, Robert
    Funke
    Heller, Michael
    Horton, P. David
    Judet, Berthe
    Klein, William
    Koslow, Michael
    Kovacs, Andrea
    Liebowitz, David Scott
    Linn, Nancy
    Nichols, G.
    P., June
    Rössler
    Sabine
    Salmiere
    Saylor, Durston
    Seidner, David
    Stanton, Mary Ellen
    Tell, Susan May
    Weiss, John
    Weston, Edward
    Zucars, Michael
    Illegible
  - Book Covers and Pages, undated (Box 7 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Color Slides (35-mm) and Transparencies, undated; (Not scanned) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Installations (Gallerie Arta, Geneva; unidentified), 1979, undated (Box 7 (hol), Folder 10)
  - International Center of Photography (Willard Straight house), undated (Box 7 (hol), Folder 11)
  - People, 1976, undated (Box 7 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Photographs (Akiba, David), undated (Box 8 (sol), Folder 10)